aldi.com.au 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy - ALDI Australia

ALDI Stores ((A Limited Partnership) ABN 90 196 565 019) ("ALDI Stores") is committed to complying with applicable privacy laws (including the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)), which set clear standards relating to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of any personal information we obtain as part of our business operations. 

ALDI Stores recognises the importance of privacy and our respect for our customers' and other individuals' right to privacy of their personal information is paramount. We have policies and procedures to ensure that all personal information is handled by us in accordance with applicable privacy laws. 

This Privacy Policy sets out:   
•Our general policies relating to management of personal information;  
•What sort of personal information we collect and the purposes for collection, how we use and disclose this information, and how we store this information; and  
•How you can obtain access to and correct any personal information we hold about you. 

If you have further questions relating to this Privacy Policy, please contact us at 1 Sargents Road Minchinbury NSW 2770, or by telephone on (02) 9675 9000. 

**What personal information do we collect?**

ALDI Stores collects personal information from customers, employees, contractors, agents and other individuals. We collect this information when it is necessary for business purposes. 

So that we can provide and improve our services, we may collect personal information such as:  
•your name  
•address  
•telephone number  
•email address,  
•other identifiers or identification and / or information about your use of our products and services. 

The personal information we collect may be provided on forms filled out by individuals (including when you register on an ALDI Stores website and when you agree to purchase products from us), when you visit an ALDI Stores website, in face-to-face meetings, email messages, telephone conversations, or from third parties. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that contact. We will collect personal information about you only from you where it is reasonable and practical to do so, or required by law. 

Generally, you have no obligation to provide any information requested by us. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, we may not be able to provide you with any products and services that depend on the collection of this information (particularly where our collection of this information is required by law). 

We may use cookie technology on our websites to provide information and services to website visitors. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes and are a necessary part of facilitating online transactions. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify you, although they do identify your browser. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. Cookies are useful to determine overall traffic patterns through our websites. If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. This may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of the services on our websites. Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet and may also use cookies to serve ads to you based on your prior visits to our website. Such cookies are useful to ensure you are shown advertisements which are relevant to you. If you only wish to opt out of targeted advertising by Google, you may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting [www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). To opt out of other advertising-related cookies, you can visit [www.youronlinechoices.com.au](http://www.youronlinechoices.com.au/). We may also disclose encrypted copies of your personal information to third party platforms such as Facebook to engage in targeted advertising on such platforms. If you wish to opt out of third party targeted advertising, please update your ad preferences on the relevant third party platform. 

We may also use mobile phone technology to track your movement within certain ALDI stores for the purpose of optimizing the merchandising and layout of our stores. If you do not wish to participate you may turn off Bluetooth and WiFi capability on your mobile device. 

Employee records are generally not subject to the Privacy Act and, therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the handling of information about employees by ALDI Stores. For information about our practices relating to employee information, please contact us directly. 

**How is personal information used and disclosed?**

The personal information we collect is confidential. Our purpose in collecting information about you is to provide you with a better website experience, to provide products or services to you and to operate our business. 

Some examples of when we may need to collect, use and disclose this information are in relation to property or supplier enquiries, for email newsletter registration, for providing customers with products and services, and for customer complaint handling. 

ALDI Stores may use your personal information to advise you of new products and services or special offers or promotions. ALDI Stores' agents or contractors from time to time may also use your personal information to provide information to you about products and services that they may offer from time to time. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information from us, or our agents, you can opt out of receiving such information when registering on an ALDI Stores website, or you may remove your name from our list by calling us on (02) 9675 9000 and asking to be removed from our mailing list. Alternatively, if we have sent you this information by email, you can use the unsubscribe link at the end of the email. In either case, please allow 5 business days for this request to be processed. 

In the course of our business, we use a range of service providers to help us maximise the quality and efficiency of our services and business operations. This means that individuals and organisations outside of ALDI Stores may sometimes have access to personal information held by ALDI Stores and may use this on behalf of ALDI Stores. We require our service providers to adhere to strict privacy guidelines and not to keep this information or use it for any unauthorised purpose. 

**Features and Functionality Provided by Third Parties; Third Party Terms**

Certain of the content, features and functionality on the Sites may be owned and operated by third parties (collectively, “Third Party Providers”).  Where indicated, such content, features and functionality, including the Gift Card Balance Check (collectively, “Third Party Content”), may be subject to separate terms and conditions.  In that event, you acknowledge that these Australian Terms of Use will not apply to your use of the Third Party Content and that you will be subject to and comply with the terms of use offered by such Third Party Providers.  You acknowledge that we are not responsible or otherwise for liable Third Party Content or the acts or omissions of Third Party Providers and that any claims or other causes of action available to you in connection with either of the foregoing will be brought against the applicable Third Party Provider(s) and not us. 

 ALDI Stores do not routinely disclose personal information to any third parties. ALDI Stores will not use or disclose any personal information about you without your consent unless:  
•required or authorised by law;  
•it is permitted by this Privacy Policy;  
•we believe this is necessary to provide you with the products or services you have requested;  
•it is necessary to implement our terms of service;  
•it is necessary to protect the rights, property or personal safety of an ALDI Stores employee, another customer, or any member of the public or ALDI Stores; or  
•some or all of the assets and operations of the business are or may be transferred to another party by way of sale of some or all of ALDI Stores' business. 

We may also share non-personal, de-identified and aggregated information for our own research or promotional purposes. Under no circumstances will we or any of our related entities sell your details to marketing agencies without your consent. 

**How do we store personal information?**

ALDI Stores will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information we hold about you and keep this information accurate and up-to-date. Your personal information may be stored in hard copy or electronically (including on secure servers in controlled facilities). ALDI Stores has security processes in place to protect personal information from misuse, loss or unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. The types of measures we take vary with the type of information and how it is collected and stored. We require our employees, agents, contractors and data processors to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by us. 

Please note that ALDI Stores may use overseas facilities to process or back-up information and, as a result, we may transfer your personal information to these overseas facilities for storage. Moreover, if problems arise with the transmission or system handling of e-mails, administrators can analyse logs in order to resolve errors. The logs contain sender, recipient, subject and name/s of any attachment/s. The body text (i.e. contents) of the e-mail is not provided and cannot be seen by administrators. This on no account reduces our commitment to safeguard your privacy. 

**Access to and correction of your personal information**

ALDI Stores may be contacted at 1 Sargents Road Minchinbury NSW 2770, or by telephone on (02) 9675 9000. 

Upon your request, we will provide you with access to any of your personal information we hold (except in limited circumstances in which it is permitted by law for us to withhold this information). If you require access to your personal information, please contact us. Of course, before we provide you with access to your personal information, we will require some proof of identity. We will usually be able to respond to your request within 14 days. 

ALDI Stores will take reasonable steps to correct any information which is found not to be accurate, complete or up-to-date. If you wish to change personal information that is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date, please contact us and we will amend this record. If you wish to have your personal information deleted, please contact us and we will take all reasonable steps to delete it unless we need to keep it for legal reasons. 

**Problems, future changes, and more information**

If ALDI Stores becomes aware of any ongoing concerns or problems concerning our privacy practices, we will take these issues seriously and work to address these concerns. If you have any further queries relating to our Privacy Policy, or you have a problem or complaint, please contact us at 1 Sargents Road Minchinbury NSW 2770 or by telephone on (02) 9675 9000. We will consider and respond to all questions and complaints, and will respond within a reasonable time in writing. 

As our business continues to evolve, our policies will be reviewed from time-to-time and may be revised. ALDI Stores reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version of the policy on its websites. The amended Privacy Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change. 

More information about privacy law is available from the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner at <http://www.oaic.gov.au/>.
